Martin P. Catherwood Library Philip R. Dankert Files /4291
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Martin P. Catherwood Library Philip R. Dankert Files
1971-1997
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations (NYSSILR)
Martin P. Catherwood Library
Dankert, Philip R.
/4291
1 cubic feet
1 linear ft.
Records (documents).
This collection consist of correspondence, memoranda, reports, and other materials from the files of Philip Dankert. The files pertain to Labor Studies, Baruch College ILR Masters Program, Metropolitan District Office Library, Rochester Extension Office Library, Buffalo Extension Office Library, Capital District Extension Office, and the Neufeld Project.
8159514
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183 kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
R. Miles, July 02, 2014
EAD encoding:
Kheel Staff, March 04, 2019
Biographical / Historical
Since 1970 Philip R. Dankert has worked building the print and electronic based collections at Catherwood. His experience acquiring the literature in the field of industrial and labor relations and human resources management is unrivaled in this country. By latest calculation, approximately 60% of the volumes on Catherwoods shelves have been acquired during his stewardship of building the foremost library of its type in North America and one of only three such libraries in the world. Phil retired in 2004.
During the time that these files were assembled Mr. Dankert served as the Assistant to the Librarian and as the Collection Development Librarian.
Scope and Contents
This collection consist of correspondence, memoranda, reports, and other materials from the files of Philip Dankert. The files pertain to Labor Studies, Baruch College ILR Masters Program, Metropolitan District Office Library, Rochester Extension Office Library, Buffalo Extension Office Library, Capital District Extension Office, and the Neufeld Project.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Dankert, Philip R.; Martin P. Catherwood Library; New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations.
8159514
- Labor Studies, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Albany - HUCC Trip, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Baruch, 1986-1987 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Baruch - ILR Masters Program, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Buffalo Office Library, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Corning (CCFL), 1984 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Extension Libraries - Correspondence/ Memos, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Ext. Library Search Committee, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- MDO - Evaluation, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Metropolitan District Office - Library (proposed), 1979-1990 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Wedding - MD Office Lib, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- MDO Libn. - Search Committee, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- MDO Search Committee, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Neufeld Project - Correspondence, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Neufeld Project, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Rochester Extension Office 2/93, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Rochester Office Library, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 17)